Guide to the Cornell Law School Dean's Office records,1888-1989.
Cornell Law School Dean's Office records, 1888-1989
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Law School Dean's Office records, 1888-1989.
18-1-75
Cornell University. School of Law.
25 cubic ft.
Correspondence, lists, subject files, memoranda, budgets, inventories and other records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, lists, subject files, memoranda, budgets, inventories and other records of the Law School, with reference to students, scholarships, donors, professional law societies, and other matters connected with the operation of the Law School.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, lists, subject files, memoranda, budgets, inventories and other records of the Law School, with reference to students, scholarships, donors, professional law societies, and other matters connected with the operation and administration of the Law School.
Also, Law School Feasibility Study, Shepley Bulfinch Richardson and Abbott, Phase 1, 1983 and Phase 2, 1984 as part of #18-1-2554.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. School of Law.; Cornell University--Students.
Subjects:
Law--Study and teaching
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to the permission of the office of origin.
NOTES
Includes collection #18-1-2554.
#18-1-2554 arranged alphabetically.
CONTAINER LIST
- Box list not online., 1917-1989 (Box 18-1-2554 1-11)
- he said " I want to use these funny quotes" Letterfile - School of Law 1888-1889 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Funds File (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Scholarship Donors 1927-1930 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Scholarships 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Scholarship Applications for 1920-1930 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Scholarships 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Scholarships Donors 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Scholarship Applications 1931-1932 Law Librarian Applications & Action Thereon (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Scholarship Applications and Awards 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Scholarship Donors 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Cooke Loan Fund 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Applications for 1932-1934 - Student Librarian Scholarships (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Law Association Loan Fund 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Cooke Loan Fund 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Scholarship Donors 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Applications for Scholarships 1934-1935 Loans, Students Librarianships and Rooms-Myron Taylor Hall (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Cooke Loan Fund 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Law Association Loan Fund 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Scholarship Donors 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Scholarships and Loans 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Scholarship Donors 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Scholarships 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Applications for Scholarships and Financial Aid 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Scholarships 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Correspondence with College and Universities re Tuition Scholarships 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Scholarships Donors 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Scholarship Letters for 1937-1938 1st Term (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Scholarship Letters for 1937-1938 2nd Term (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Applications for Scholarships, Assistant Librarianships, and Rooms in Myron Taylor Hall 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Scholarships Donors 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Applications for Scholarships, Loans, Librarianships, etc. 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Correspondence re Tuition Scholarships 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Donors 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Correspondence re: Tuition Scholarships 1939-1940. (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Scholarship Letters, 1st and 2nd Terms 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Donors File 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Donors File 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Donor File 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Scholarship Letters 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Donor File 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Correspondence with Students and Mr. Roqalsky re: Award of Scholarships, Loans, and Librarianships 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Donor File 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Applications -for Scholarships, Loans, Rooms, .etc. 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Scholarships and Fellowships 1928-1930 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Memorandums of Interviews A-C (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Memorandums of Interviews D-M (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Memorandums of Interviews N-Z (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Applicants for Faculty Appointments 1925-1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Applicants for Faculty Appointments 1939-1941 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Applicants for Faculty Appointments 1941-1945 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Lecture Notes on "The History and Evolution of The Law" etc., by Judge Francis M., Finch (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Financial Records 1914-1919 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Report of the Dean 1921-1936 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Annual Financial Statements 1931-1942 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- College of Law Appropriations 1902-1922 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Business Office Miscellaneous 1906-1910 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Legislation 1909-1913 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Colleges of Law Administration Regulations 1916-1920 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Class Lists, Assignments to Faculty Advisors, Class Standings, Scholarships, Registration by Courses, Probation List 1931 - 1932 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Class Lists etc. 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder l6)
- Class Lists etc. 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Class Lists etc. 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Cornell Law Quarterly (Box 3 (overstuffed), Folder 1-2)
- Contracts Annotation Committee 1928-1932 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Annotation of Contracts Restatement 1927-1930 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Class Lists, Ranks, etc. 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Class Lists, Ranks, etc. 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Class Lists, Ranks, etc. 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Class Lists, Ranks, etc. 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Copies of Affidavits and Letters for Mr. Gibson 1940 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Copies of Affidavits and Letters for Mr. Gibson 1941 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Selective Service 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Student Statement of Information 1941 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Future Sction - Statements of Information 1941 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- First Year Students - Statements of Information, Affidavits, Letters 1940 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Second Year Students - Statements of Information, Affidavits, Letters 1940 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Second Year - Copies of Affidavits and Letters for Mr. Gibson 1940 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Class Lists, etc. 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Class Lists, etc. 1936-37 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Class Lists, etc. 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Class Lists, etc. 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Class Lists, etc. 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Class Lists, etc. 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Old Budgets 1919-1934 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Budgets - Summer Sessions 1928-1937 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Questionnaires of American Bar Association 1928-1938 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Requirements for Admission to the Bar - 1927 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- American Arbitration Association 1944 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Joint Conference on Legal Education 1932-1938 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- American Law Book Co. 1923-1929 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- American Law Book Co. 1930-1942 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Joint Conf. on Legal Education 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Bar Exams and Legal Education, Joint Conf. 1932 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Joint Conf. on Legal Education 1941-1944 (Box 4, Folder 1l)
- Delta Chi Correspondence 1921-1923 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Moot Court (Box 4, Folder 13)
- American Arbitration Association (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Assoc. of American Law Schools 1941 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Reports 1936-1941 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Association of American Law Schools 1923-1934 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- American Bar Association 1922-1939 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- American Bar Association 1933-1940 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- American Bar Association 1940-1944 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Myron Taylor Hall re: Building, Equipment, Furnishings, etc. 1928-1932 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Dedication of Myron Taylor Hall 1932 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Myron Taylor Hall - Sculpture (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Myron Taylor Hall - Lighting (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Law Officials - Alumni State of New York (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Letters from Law Alumni re: Report (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Ashbery Trips - 1931-1932 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Letter to Alumni 1932 (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
- Alumni Report 1938 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Commencement 1933 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Commencement 1934 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Commencement 1935 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Commencement 1936 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Commencement 1937 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Commencement 1939-1941 (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
- Who's Who 1907-1914 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Entrance Requirements - Report and Correspondence 1917 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Inventory of Non-Student Files of Law School
  - Ackerman, Mrs. Mary Linton (5 items) (Box 7)
  - Adams, Joseph Q. (Box 7)
  - Adams, Arthur G. (Box 7)
  - Adamson, Robert (Box 7)
  - Advertizing (Box 7)
  - Agate, John H. (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Alden, Carlos C. (Box 7)
  - Aldrich, Byron S. (Box 7)
  - Alien, Herrick C. (Box 7)
  - Altman, William (Box 7)
  - Alumni-Law Officials, State of Hew York (Box 7)
  - Alumni, Letter to (Box 7)
  - American Association of Teachers of Journalism (Box 7)
  - American Committee for Guidance of Professional Personnel (Box 7)
  - American Council on Education 1943-1945 (Box 7)
  - American Foundation (Box 7)
  - American Institute of Accountants (Box 7)
  - American Institute of Comparative Law and Legislation (Box 7)
  - American Correspondence School of Law (Box 7)
  - American Law Institute (Box 7)
  - American Law Students Association (Box 7)
  - American Legion (Box 7)
  - American-Scandanavian Foundation (Box 7)
  - Anderson, E. H. (Box 7)
  - Anderson, R.P. (Box 7)
  - Angell, James H. (Box 7)
  - Anniversary of the Law School (Box 7)
  - Announcement 1948-1949 (Box 7)
  - Annual Financial Statements 1928-1943 (Box 7)
  - Arbuckle, Walter ¥. (Box 7)
  - Army Specialized Training Program (Box 7)
  - Armstrong, George T. (Box 7)
  - Arts College 1923-1923 (Box 7)
  - Arts College Conference ( esp. Robert Ferrari ) (Box 7)
  - Arts Conferences (Box 7)
  - Ashley, Dean Clarence D. (Box 7)
  - Ashton, Henry H. (Box 7)
  - Assistant Librarian, Applications (Box 7)
  - Association of American Law Schools (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Association of Bar of the City of New York (Box 7)
  - Athletic Association (Relation of Faculty to) (Box 7)
  - Atkinson, Thomas E. (Box 7)
  - Automobiles, Report on Student Ownership of 1930 (Box 7)
  - Ayer, Leslie J. (Box 7)
  - "A" Miscellaneous 1929-1934, 1934-1939 (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Babcock, Herbert N. (Box 7)
  - Bacon, George W. (Box 7)
  - Bailey, Liberty Hyde (Box 7)
  - Baker, J. Newton (Box 7)
  - Baker, Voorhis & Co. (Box 7)
  - Balogh, Elmer (Box 7)
  - Bancroft - Whitney Co. (Box 7)
  - Bangs, Edwin M. (Box 7)
  - Bangs, Francis S. (Box 7)
  - Banks & Company, Law Book Publishers (Box 7)
  - Bannister, L. Ward (Box 7)
  - Bar Association, Preliminary Certificates (Box 7)
  - Bar Examining Committee, Connecticut (Box 7)
  - Bar Association Conference at Washington 1922 (Box 7)
  - Bar Requirements (Box 7)
  - Barber, C.G. (Box 7)
  - Barmore Collection (The) (Box 7)
  - Barringer, Benjamin L. (Box 7)
  - Barrister's Ball (Box 7)
  - Barthold, Mendelssohn (Box 7)
  - Barton, Col. Frank A. (Box 7)
  - Bates, Dean Henry W. (Box 7)
  - Bauer, John (Box 7)
  - Bayer, Charles (Box 7)
  - Beahan, Willard (Box 7)
  - Beale, Joseph H. (Box 7)
  - Bebb, Hubert C. (Box 7)
  - Becker, Carl (Box 7)
  - Beers, George E. (Box 7)
  - Beitz, William E. (Box 7)
  - Bender, Matthew & Co. (Box 7)
  - Bennett, Earl J. (Box 7)
  - Bennett, Lawerence (Box 7)
  - Berry, Romeyn (Box 7)
  - Betten, Cornelius (Box 7)
  - Bigelow, Fanny (Box 7)
  - Bills, Benjamin (Box 7)
  - Bingham, Joseph (Box 7)
  - Birdseye, Clarence F. (Box 7)
  - Blackmar, Hon. Abel E. (3 items) (Box 7)
  - Blauvelt, George A. (Box 7)
  - Bleakley, William F. (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Bley, C.F. (Box 7)
  - Bobbs - Merrill Co. (Box 7)
  - Bogert. George G. (Box 7)
  - Bonner, Griffith (Box 7)
  - Boochever, Louis (Box 7)
  - Bool, H.J. Co. (Box 7)
  - Booth, Walter C. (Box 7)
  - Bostwick, Charles D. (Box 7)
  - Bradbury, H.B. (Box 8)
  - Bradford, Prof. Eugene (7 items) (Box 8)
  - Breene, C. M. (Box 8)
  - Brennan and De Angelis (Box 8)
  - Brewer, Isaac W. (Box 8)
  - Bride, William W. (Box 8)
  - Brierly, James L. (Box 8)
  - Bristol, Arthur E. (Box 8)
  - Bristol, Everett (Box 8)
  - Brooklyn Bar Association (Box 8)
  - Brooks, President Stratton D. (Box 8)
  - Brown, Anan (Box 8)
  - Brown, Frederick W. (Box 8)
  - Brown, Harlan (Box 8)
  - Brown, Rome G. (Box 8)
  - Bruce, Dean Andrew A. (Box 8)
  - Bryant, Theodore K. (Box 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds 1927-1939, 1940-1945 (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Bull, Lieut. Henry C. (Box 8)
  - Burch, Rousseau A. (Box 8)
  - Burdick, Charles K. (Box 8)
  - Burdick, Francis M. (Box 8)
  - Burford, Waldo (Box 8)
  - Burkan, Nathan Memorial Competition 1945 (Box 8)
  - "B" Miscellaneous (Box 8)
  - Cady, Edwin W. (Box 8)
  - Callaghan and Company, Law Publishers (Box 8)
  - Camptell, Prof. Morton C. (Box 8)
  - Camptell, W.A. (Box 8)
  - Cardozo, Benjamin (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Carnergie Corporation of New York (Box 8)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace (Box 8)
  - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Carpenter, Professor Charles E. (Box 8)
  - Catterall, Professor Ralph (Box 8)
  - Charnwood, Lord (Box 8)
  - Chase, Willis (Box 8)
  - Cheatham, Elliott (Box 8)
  - Cherry. Professor Wilbur (Box 8)
  - Chilean General Scientific Conference (Box 8)
  - Christian, Mr. M.B. (Box 8)
  - Clark, Professor Charles E. (Box 8)
  - Clark, Henry C. (Box 8)
  - Clark, HA (Box 8)
  - Clark University (Box 8)
  - Coffin, Foster (Box 8)
  - Cohn, Morris M. (Box 8)
  - Coleman, J.M. (Box 8)
  - Collegiate Special Advertising Company (Box 8)
  - Collier, Charles S. (Box 8)
  - Colson, Frederick D. (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Colvin, George E. (Box 8)
  - Committee of Status of Extension Staff (Box 8)
  - Committee on Student Affairs 1916-1922, 1923-1928 (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Committee of University Policy (Box 8)
  - Commencement Tickets, 1923, 1926, 1927 (Box 8)
  - Commercial Law League of America (Box 8)
  - Committee on Loan Funds 1924-1926 (Box 8)
  - "Comparative Law" (Box 8)
  - Comparative Law Bureau of the American Bar Association (Box 8)
  - Comprehensive Examinations (Box 8)
  - Conference of Legal Education (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Congressional Committee of Reviaion of the Laws (Box 8)
  - Cook, Prof. Walter W. (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Cooke, Walter P. (Box 8)
  - Cooley, Prof. Roger (Box 8)
  - Cooper, Robert J. (Box 8)
  - Corbin, Prof. Arthur L. (Box 8)
  - Cordon, A.C. (Box 8)
  - Cornell Alumni Society of Washington (Box 8)
  - Cornell, Edward (Box 8)
  - Costigan, George P. Jr. (Box 8)
  - Coville, Dr. Luzerne (Box 8)
  - Crane, Hon. Frederick E. (Box 8)
  - Crane, Dean T. F. (Box 8)
  - Crane, Prof. Judson A. (Box 8)
  - Crane and McGlenen (Box 8)
  - Creighton, Dean J.E. (Box 8)
  - Crofts, George D. (Box 8)
  - Cronk, Joseph A. (Box 8)
  - Crouch, Leonard C. (Box 8)
  - Crowder, General Enoch H. (Box 8)
  - Currier, Prof, Richard D. (Box 8)
  - Curtis, C.E., Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds (Box 8)
  - "C "Miscellaneous (Box 8)
  - Curtis Publishing Co. (Box 8)
  - Danaher, Franklin M., Sec. and Treasurer of the State Board of Law Examiner (Box 8)
  - Dann, Prof. Hollis (Box 8)
  - Davis, Hon. Borland L. (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - de Jesus, Anjil (Box 8)
  - DeMonde, Agnes (Box 8)
  - Dewey, Prof. John (Box 8)
  - Dicker, Samuel B. (Box 8)
  - Dobie, Prof. Armistead (Box 8)
  - Downing, Hon. Augustus (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Dransfield, Mary Caldwell (Box 8)
  - Drew, Prof. William (Box 8)
  - Dugan, William J. (Box 8)
  - Dunn, Dean Henry W. (Box 8)
  - Darand, William J. (Box 8)
  - Durham, Prof. Charles Love (Box 8)
  - "D" Miscellaneous (Box 8)
  - Eagle Information Bureau (BROOKLYN DAILY EAGLE) (Box 9)
  - Edgerton, Henry White (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Edlund, R, C. (President Schurman's Secretary) (Box 9)
  - Edwards, Harold T. (Box 9)
  - Eidlits and Hulse (Box 9)
  - Ellner, Josenh (re University of Michigan Legal Center) (Box 9)
  - Empire State Furnishing Company (1 item) (Box 9)
  - Employment 1925 (Box 9)
  - Employment 1925-1926 (Box 9)
  - Employment in Myron Taylor Hall, Applications (Box 9)
  - von Engeln, O.D. (Prof.- 1 piece) (Box 9)
  - Engineering Law Course (Box 9)
  - Entrance Requirements (Box 9)
  - Evans, Mr. F.C., Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds (4 items) (Box 9)
  - Evans, M. E., Fargo, N.D. (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Everett, Professor, G. A. (l item) (Box 9)
  - Ewald, Henry Jr. (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Ewart, John S. (Box 9)
  - Ewing, John K.M (Box 9)
  - Ewinf, Thomas (Box 9)
  - "E" Miscellaneous (Box 9)
  - Faculty (3 folders- Research, Vacancy, Miscellaneous) (Box 9)
  - Fagan, Hugh J. (3 items) (Box 9)
  - Fairchild, falter (Box 9)
  - Family Life, Courses in (Box 9)
  - Farrand, President Livingston Jan. 1929-Dec. 1931, 1932-1937, 1927-1928, 1926, 1923-1925, 1921-1922 (6 folders) (Box 9)
  - Federation of Bar Association (Box 9)
  - Federal Law Revision, Criminal(l piece) (Box 9)
  - Ferson, Merton L. (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Fiero, J. Newton (Box 9)
  - Finch, William Albert (Box 9)
  - Fire Prevention (Box 9)
  - Fish, Dr. P. A. (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Fiske, G, Walter Prof. ( 4 items) (Box 9)
  - Foose, A.M. (Box 9)
  - Foreign Area and Language Training (Box 9)
  - Foreign Service (Box 9)
  - Foreign Students, Re- Entrance (6 items) (Box 9)
  - Forster, Henry A. (4 items) (Box 9)
  - Forrest, George M. (Box 9)
  - Foundation, Research (Box 9)
  - Foundation Press Inc. (Box 9)
  - Fraser, Dean E. (6 items) (Box 9)
  - Fraser, Elizabeth (Box 9)
  - Fraser, Henry (Box 9)
  - Frankfurter, Felix (Box 9)
  - Fraser Scholarships (Box 9)
  - Fraser, Everett (Box 9)
  - Freshman, Edward A. (3 items) (Box 9)
  - Frey, H.A. (3 items) (Box 9)
  - Frierson, J. Nelson (4 items) (Box 9)
  - Fuller, William P. (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Fulton, Heivell C. (2 items) (Box 9)
  - "F" General (Box 9)
  - Gallagher, L.H. (l item) (Box 9)
  - Gannett, Frank E. (3 items) (Box 9)
  - Garside, Charles (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Gay, C.W. (l item) (Box 9)
  - Geneva University, Switzerland (Box 9)
  - George Washington Bicentennial Commission (Box 9)
  - Georgetown University School of Law (invitation to 50th anniversary) (Box 9)
  - Gifford, Ralph (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Gribbs, Dean B.C. (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Gilmore, Prof. Eugene (Box 9)
  - Glushieu, Morris P. (Box 9)
  - Goble, Prof. George (Box 9)
  - Goodelle, Hon. William P. (l item) (Box 9)
  - Goodner, Prof. Ivan W. (l item) (Box 9)
  - Gorewitz, Joseph (Box 9)
  - Gould, Prof. Gino (Box 9)
  - Grace, Mrs. Anna (Box 9)
  - Grace, Charles Henry Estate See Rogalsky (Box 9)
  - Gregory, Dean Charles Noble (Box 9)
  - Graduate Record Examinations (Box 9)
  - Graduate School (Box 9)
  - Graduation with honors (Box 9)
  - Graton Louis (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Gregory, Charles 0. (Box 9)
  - Groser, Leslie H. (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Group Insurance (Box 9)
  - Guerin W.E. Jr. (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Guthrie, William D. (Box 9)
  - "G" Miscellaneous (Box 9)
  - Hall, Dean Allen C. (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Hall, H.H. (Hobart College- 3 items) (Box 9)
  - Hall, James Parker (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Hamburg, Alexander (Box 9)
  - Hamilton, Edgar A. (Box 9)
  - Hamilton, James (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Hammond, Prof. William A. (3 folders) (Box 9)
  - Hampden County (Mass.) Law Library (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Hantrury, Harold (Box 9)
  - Hand, Judge Learned (Box 9)
  - Handler, Milton (Box 9)
  - Harno, Dean Albert J. (Box 9)
  - Harker, Dean Oliver (Box 9)
  - HARLOW'S WEEKLY (3 items) (Box 9)
  - Harmon, Charles M. (Box 9)
  - Harris, Prof. G. D. (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Harrison, Frank (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Harrold, James P. (Box 9)
  - Hart, Harold (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Hartzell Charles R. (Box 9)
  - Harvard Failed Students Admitted to Cornell (Box 9)
  - Harvard Law School (Box 9)
  - Hastings, Dean W. G. (l item) (Box 9)
  - Haupin, G. D. Assistant Cornell Registrar (Box 9)
  - Haverbeck, Harrison M. (Box 9)
  - Hayes, Alfred (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Hayes, H.B. (1 item) (Box 9)
  - Hazard, Hon. Fredericks. (Box 9)
  - Heard, Mrs. O.P. (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Heckscher Council Grant # 177 (Box 9)
  - Hewitt, Prof. Waterman T. (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Hickok, Prof. Charles T. (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Hill, President A. Ross (of Univ. of Missouri - 3 items) (Box 9)
  - Hillick, A.A. (l item) (Box 9)
  - Hinchliff, Emerson (6 items) (Box 9)
  - Hirshfeld, Prof, C.F. (2 items) (Box 9)
  - Hiscock, Frank H. (3 folders) (Box 9)
  - Hodges, Hon Earl (l item) (Box 10)
  - Hodges. President Thomas E« (Box 10)
  - Hodson, Hon Devoe (3 items) (Box 10)
  - Hogate, Been Enoch "(3 items) (Box 10)
  - Hollands, Hon. Joseph. H. (1 item) (Box 10)
  - Holt, Judge George C. (2 items) (Box 10)
  - Hoogesteger, J.D. (2 items) (Box 10)
  - Hooker, John P. (3 items) (Box 10)
  - Hope, Theodore Jr. (Box 10)
  - Hough, Hon. Charles M. (Box 10)
  - Houghton, George (l item) (Box 10)
  - Housing women students (Box 10)
  - Howard University (Box 10)
  - Howes, Raymond (Box 10)
  - Hoy, David F. (3 folders) (Box 10)
  - Hoyt, George W. Estate - see Meigs (Box 10)
  - Hubbard, Arthur (3 items) (Box 10)
  - Hubbard, General Thomas H. (Box 10)
  - Hubbell, C.U. (2 items ) (Box 10)
  - Hubbell Publishing Co. (Box 10)
  - Hubbs, Hon. Irving G. (Box 10)
  - Hudsomp Manley (Box 10)
  - Huffcut, Miss Lillian (Box 10)
  - Hughes, Hon. Charles Evans (Box 10)
  - Hunkin, S.E. (2 items) (Box 10)
  - Hunt, Everette, H. (l item) (Box 10)
  - Hyatt, Roger C. (Box 10)
  - Humphrey, William F. (Printer) (Box 10)
  - Hutchins, Harry B. ( Pres. Univ. of Michigan) (Box 10)
  - "H" Miscellaneous (3 folders) (Box 10)
  - Ickes, Hon. Harold L. (Box 10)
  - Illinois, Univ. of - College of Law (Box 10)
  - Inter- American Academy of Comparative and International Law (Box 10)
  - Inauguration of President Farrand (Box 10)
  - Institute of International Education (Box 10)
  - Iowa Aptitude Tests (Box 10)
  - Irvine Lecture Find (Box 10)
  - Irvine, Judge Frank (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - "I" Miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Jackson, F. Ellis (Box 10)
  - James, Pres. Edmund (University of Illinois) (Box 10)
  - Jamws, Laylin K. (Box 10)
  - Jenks, Prof. J. W. (Box 10)
  - John Hopkins Univ., Institute of Law (Box 10)
  - Johnson, Eads (Box 10)
  - Johnson, Peter (l item) (Box 10)
  - Jonas, Albert (4 items) (Box 10)
  - Jones, Arthur H. (2 items) (Box 10)
  - Jones, Dean H. C. (Box 10)
  - Jones, Horace L. (Prof. 2 items) (Box 10)
  - Jones, Henry Craig (Box 10)
  - Jones, John (2 items) (Box 10)
  - Jones, Prof William Carey (2 items) (Box 10)
  - Jordan, Dr. (l item) (Box 10)
  - Judges, Law Alumni, State of New York (Box 10)
  - Jury, John C. (Box 10)
  - "J" Miscellaneous (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Kales, Albert M. (Box 10)
  - Karelson, Frank E. Jr. (3 items) (Box 10)
  - Keeler, Hon. Harvey R. (l item) (Box 10)
  - Kehoe, H. (3 items) (Box 10)
  - Kelley, Charles E. (Box 10)
  - Kemmerer, Prof E.W. (2 items) (Box 10)
  - Kimball, Dean Dexter S. (Box 10)
  - Kimbel, Prof. B.W. (Box 10)
  - Zing, Prof E.E. (Box 10)
  - Kirckwey, Prof, George (2 items) (Box 10)
  - Kiikwood, Dean M.R. (Box 10)
  - Kitchenette, Myron Taylor Hall (Box 10)
  - Knowles, L. R. (Box 10)
  - Kuhn, Capt. John N. (Box 10)
  - Kuhnert, Dr. Hellmot (Box 10)
  - "K" Miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Ladd Dean Carl E. (Box 10)
  - Laidlaw, William K (Box 10)
  - Lane, Kenneth B. (Box 10)
  - Lane, V. H. (2 items) (Box 10)
  - Lawerence, Dean Thomas A. (Box 10)
  - Laski, Prof. Harold (Box 10)
  - Laveny, Prof. Thomas C. (Box 10)
  - Lauterpacht, Prof. H. (Box 10)
  - Law, John W. ( 3 items) (Box 10)
  - Law Clubs (Box 10)
  - Law Faculty Committees (Box 10)
  - Law Revision (Box 10)